[
    [
        {
            "question" : "20 * 20",
            "answer" : [400, 240, 420]
        },
        {
            "question" : "35 * 10",
            "answer" : [520, 123, 350]
        },
        {
            "question" : "15 * 18",
            "answer" : [270, 225, 30]
        },
        {
            "question" : "22 * 11",
            "answer" : [222, 242, 121]
        },
        {
            "question" : "82 * 7",
            "answer" : [574, 234, 564]
        },
        {
            "question" : "45 / 3",
            "answer" : [42, 15, 135]
        },
        {
            "question" : "121 + 653",
            "answer" : [774, 522, 500]
        },
        {
            "question" : "34 * 18",
            "answer" : [345, 233, 612]
        },
        {
            "question" : "215 - 603",
            "answer" : [818, -388, 388]
        },
        {
            "question" : "121 + 96",
            "answer" : [217, 322, 25]
        },
        {
            "question" : "41 * 21",
            "answer" : [200, 420, 861]
        },
        {
            "question" : "23 * 23",
            "answer" : [529, 295, 46]
        },
        {
            "question" : "65 / 5",
            "answer" : [60, 13, 19]
        },
        {
            "question" : "55 * 8",
            "answer" : [440, 220, 144]
        },
        {
            "question" : "456 + 123",
            "answer" : [600, 121, 579]
        },
        {
            "question" : "999 - 542",
            "answer" : [80, 457, 745]
        },
        {
            "question" : "741 - 963",
            "answer" : [222, 100, -222]
        },
        {
            "question" : "18 * 36",
            "answer" : [648, 54, 180]
        },
        {
            "question" : "123 + 123",
            "answer" : [246, 814, 512]
        },
        {
            "question" : "52 * 16",
            "answer" : [422, 832, 400]
        },
        {
            "question" : "460 / 5",
            "answer" : [465, 142, 92]
        },
        {
            "question" : "246 + 451",
            "answer" : [121, 697, 740]
        },
        {
            "question" : "365 + 159",
            "answer" : [524, 245, 90]
        },
        {
            "question" : "525 / 15",
            "answer" : [540, 205, 35]
        },
        {
            "question" : "35 * 24",
            "answer" : [456, 800, 840]
        },
        {
            "question" : "582 - 365",
            "answer" : [217, 182, 86]
        },
        {
            "question" : "21 * 36",
            "answer" : [400, 212, 756]
        },
        {
            "question" : "840 / 14",
            "answer" : [59, 60, 51]
        },
        {
            "question" : "324 - 587",
            "answer" : [-263, 326, 222]
        },
        {
            "question" : "589 + 409",
            "answer" : [999, 998, 899]
        }
    ]
]
